

Shashank Bhattacharya

Javascript Developer

- New Delhi, India
- +91 8447997069
- shwshank3@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/ shashank-bhattacharya-58aa6879/
- github.com/Shwshank
- m shwshank.github.io

EDUCATION-

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science - UPTU 2010 - 2014

Highschool- CBSE India 2009-2010

SKILLS -

- Angular, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3
- Redux, React, Protector, Jest
- o D3, E-Charts, Data Visualization
- PWA, SPA, TDD, Sass
- NodeJS, ExpessJS, Mongoose
- REST API, GraphQL
- Lodash, Passport, Redis
- ∘ S3, EC2, Firebase
- Serverless
- o Git, Phabricator, Jenkins
- Salesforce Certified Administrator

SUMMARY -

Javascript developer with more than 3years of experience in building interactive web applications and an active community member of opensource projects.

I have worked on a few SaaS projects and some of existing modules which I migrated on advanced platforms. Most of the time I have worked on front-end analyzing optimal user experience, and sometimes developing backend applications.

EXPERIENCE -

Front End Developer

Quality Council of India, New Delhi

August 2017- PRESENT

I am working in QCI, developing & maintaining web applications for various departments of the government. Developing highly scalable applications with ease of access to interact with maintaining quality.

Full Stack Developer

Invidev, New Delhi

January - August 2017

I was part of core development team, ensuring delivery and maintenance of high-end projects from the very scratch. Being working in a startup, I was able to get myself involved in working on all of the phases of SDLC

Technical Support Engineer

HCL, Noida

April 2015 - December 2016

Salesforce Certified Administrator, worked on Salesforce and Pearson Vue projects while working in HCL. I was part of the team providing technical assistance to professional users of Pearson Vue, using Salesforce as their CRM platform.

Founding Member, Developer

Innovative Meds, New Delhi

March2014 - January 2015

I along with my team was developing an online platform for the record keeping of prescription issued by the doctor to the patients. Future scope of the platform was to advise patients with respect to the data gathered.